

Contact

Phone

+92 324 3329192

Email

mshahzaib101ed@gmail.com

Address

Karachi, Pakistan

Portfolio

https://iamshahzaib.com/ https://github.com/mshahzaib101

Expertise

- Javascript
- React js
- Node js
- Next.js
- Gatsby.js
- Firebase
- Express.js
- AWS
- Fastify.js
- React Native
- MongoDB
- Python
- Mailchimp/Hubspot
- Graphql
- Html & CSS
- Docker
- Tensorflow
- GCP

Muhammad Shahzaib

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

I am Shahzaib, Full-stack developer from UAE / Pakistan with a focus on React.js Development for the last 4+ years. I have specialized in responsive web and application development for startups and small to medium size businesses. My skill set includes wide-ranging expertise in Javascript frameworks such as React.js, Next.js and Gatsby.js. I am also great at Node.js, Bootstrap, Firebase, AWS, MongoDB, Python and a whole host of other technologies, and libraries. Whatever your needs are, I will find a solution that fits it.

Experience

Q 2020 - Present

Vaionex I Delaware, USA

Full-stack developer, Lead developer

I am working as a Full-stack and Lead developer at Vaionex since last 2 years. Vaionex provides blockchain solutions.

2019 - 2020

Upwork I US

Full-stack developer

I started my freelance career as Fulltime work. I worked with 20+ clients mostly building Single Page Applications on React and providing bug-fixing services.

2019 - 2019

Hasati I California, US

MERN-stack developer

I was working part-time as a MERN developer in Hasati. I was mostly working on React.js and Node.js. It was a remote job.

2018 - 2019

Axiom I Pakistan

Front-end developer

I was working part-time as a front-end developer in Axiom. I was mostly working on React.js.

Education

O 2018 - 2020

Cambridge A'levels UK GCSE

I am working as a Full-stack and Lead developer at Vaionex since last 2 years. Vaionex provides blockchain solutions.

2018

Cambridge O'levels UK GCSE

I did my Cambridge Olevel UK GCSE in Accounting and Finance